(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
hololive 3rd Generation Live
Operation Kyururun
~The Strongest Idols, You Have No Choice But To Support Them~
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
録音・録画・アップロードは禁止されています
Recording, filming, and uploading are prohibited.
スクリーンショットはOKです！SNSへアップして応援しよう！
Screenshots are OK! Upload them to social media to show your support!
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to the nature of the performance, please be aware of flashing lights.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering and shouting your support is OK.
2次販売グッズ
Second Round of Merchandise Sales
hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
hololive 3rd Generation Live
Operation Kyururun
~The Strongest Idols, You Have No Choice But To Support Them~
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
きゅるるん大作戦
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun
~The Strongest Idols, You Can't Help But Stan Them~
たくさんの素敵なショート動画ありがとうございました！ぜひ「あいあいあいあいにじゅー」をたくさん使って投稿してくださいね！
Thank you for all the wonderful short videos! Please post lots of videos using "I-I-I-I-I Need You"!
だーから　君のこと　大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き　大好き
So, I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you!
溢れるこの想い　きっと　もっと　止まらない
These overflowing feelings, surely, more and more, won't stop!
I-I-I-I-I Love You
I-I-I-I-I Need You
もっと！　ぎゅっと！
More! Tightly!
...好きなだけ愛させて
...Let me love you as much as I want
夢見るハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming heart goes hop, hop, hop
あんなに堕ちてアミャアミャ
Falling so deep, it's all mushy
こんなになっても今だ抜け出せない！
Even now, I still can't get out!
どうしたもんかのニュイニュイニュイ
What should I do? Nyui nyui nyui
助けて君たちアホイホイ
Help me, everyone! Ahoy-hoy!
まったまったまった...
Wait, wait, wait...
好きなだけ愛してね！
Please love me as much as you want!
ありがとうございました！ぜひ「あいあいあいあい♡あいらぶゆー」を使って動画を作ってみてください！
Thank you very much! Please try making videos
using "Ai Ai Ai Ai I Love You"!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon
Please wait a moment.
The concert will be starting soon.
ハッシュタグ #きゅるるん大作戦
Feel free to share screenshots and talk about the live with #きゅるるん大作戦
Hashtag #KyururunDaisakusen
Feel free to share screenshots and talk about
the live with #KyururunDaisakusen
Sponsors 協賛
Sponsors
アニメにハマって 歌いたくなっちゃった
I got hooked on anime and felt like singing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
Being able to sing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてツライッ！
It's so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND
全国のアミューズメント施設にて ホロライブ3期生 プライズ順次展開中！
Hololive 3rd Gen prizes are now rolling out at amusement facilities nationwide!
吉野家でごはんにしよ♪
Let's have a meal at Yoshinoya♪
ぎゅう
Beef
ぎゅうぎゅう
Beef, beef
ぎゅぅ〜
Beeeef~
うま！
Delicious!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Taste the seriousness of the original.
牛丼は吉野家
For beef bowls, it's Yoshinoya.
やっぱこれだね
It's got to be this.
ホロライブ3期生 ミニCDコレクション
Hololive 3rd Gen Mini CD Collection
ホロライブ3期生 つながるあにまるらばすと
Hololive 3rd Gen Connecting Animal Rubber Straps
きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun ~The strongest idols, you just have to support them~
3期生ライブ開催おめでとうございます！
Congratulations on the 3rd Generation Live!
全力で楽しんで！最高の思い出にしよう！
Enjoy it with all your might! Let's make it the best memory!
マリン船長大好き！応援してるよ！
I love Captain Marine! I'm cheering for you!
hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦 〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
hololive 3rd Generation Live:
Operation Kyururun - The Ultimate Idols, You Have No Choice But To Stan
せーの！
One, two!
はじまるわ！
It's starting!
hololive 3rd Generation Live きゅるるん大作戦 〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜 にご来場いただき...
Welcome to hololive 3rd Generation Live: Operation Kyururun - The Ultimate Idols, You Have No Choice But To Stan...
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、
To ensure everyone enjoys the live show until the end,
いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
please allow me to provide some information.
公演中の撮影、録音、
Photography, audio recording,
録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
and the use of recording equipment are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。
Smoking is prohibited inside the building.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from smoking.
万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, do not overdo it
近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
and please notify a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Acts such as moshing, diving, or throwing things onto the stage,
他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
or any behavior that disrupts the show is strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね。
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
Also, cameras for video distribution and photography will be present,
客席が映り込む場合があります。
and the audience may be captured on film.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可の...
These videos and photos may be used for pro...
可能性がありますので、ほらー!
...motion and such, so—See!
あらかじめご了承ください。
Please understand this in advance.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#きゅるるん大作戦Day1」です。
The hashtag for the show is "#きゅるるん大作戦Day1".
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you used the hashtag to help build the excitement.
それでは、開演までもう少しです。
Well then, there is just a little while left until the show begins.
みんなの声をたくさん聞かせてぺこ!
Let me hear everyone's voices, peko!
それじゃあ3期生、円陣行くかー!
Alright 3rd Generation, let's do our huddle!
みんな、今からマイクがなくなるので、静かに、静かに。
Everyone, the mics will be off from now on, so be quiet, be quiet.
Kアリーナ 横浜
きゅるるん大作戦
K-Arena Yokohama
Operation Kyururun
兎田ぺこら
Usada Pekora
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
白銀ノエル
Shirogane Noel
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦 〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun ~The Strongest Idols, You Can't Help But Support Them~
I I I I love you
も I I I I need you
And I I I I need you
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want
3rdライブ、いくぜー！
3rd Live, here we go!
みんなで最高の思い出、作ろうね！
Let's make the best memories together!
狂るるの無いキミだらけ
Dizzying thoughts of nothing but you
どうかしてるわね、私
I've gone a bit crazy, haven't I?
心臓ドキドキなってる、Hey, Ho!
My heart is pounding, Hey, Ho!
毎日幻覚あらわれて
Hallucinations appear every day
頭に花咲いちゃって
Flowers are blooming in my head
恋ってやつは非常識ですわ
Love is a crazy thing
いっそ食べちゃいたい
I almost want to eat it up
フリーズした感情
My frozen emotions
誰もが持ってる、お願い
Everyone has a wish, please
純、純、純情エモーション
Pure, pure, pure emotion
ドドドド急上昇
Surging up rapidly
これが恋ならもう後悔しないわ
If this is love, I won't regret it anymore
だから！
So!
君の事大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き！
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you!
あふれるこの愛はずっと
This overflowing love will always
もっと止まらない
Keep on going without stopping
I I I I love you
君が I I I I need you
You are the one I I I I need
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want
揺れるハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My fluttering heart goes hop-hop-hop
穴に落ちてあびゃびゃ
Falling into a hole, dizzy with love
こんなになっても今だ抜け出せない
Even now, I still can't get out of this
どうしたもんかねヌイヌイヌイ
What should I do, nui nui nui?
助けて君旅アホイホイ
Help me, your journey, Ahoy-hoy!
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
好きなだけ愛してね
Please love me as much as you want
ふわっふわっ夢のなか
Fluffy, fluffy, inside a dream
君の声で目が覚めた
Your voice woke me up
五感全部が君のシグナル
All my senses are signals from you
毎度お騒がせごめん
Sorry for the constant commotion
キュンで壊れちゃいそうだ
Feels like I'm going to break from this spark
恋ってやつは制御不能ですわ
Love is something uncontrollable
いっそ抱きしめて
Just go ahead and hug me
壊してもいいよ
You can even break me
誰にも邪魔はさせない
I won't let anyone get in the way
ピチピチ感情で
With fresh, lively feelings
キラキラ急展開
A sparkling, sudden turn of events
これが運命ならもう迷わない
If this is fate, I won't hesitate anymore
覚悟してね！
Get ready for it!
君だけが大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き！
I love only you, love you, love you, love you, love you!
私のこの愛はずっと
This love of mine will always
ずっともっと離さない
Never let go, more and more
Be be be my baby
and kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss to me
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
私だけを見ててね
Only look at me, okay?
無視たろは泣いちゃうかもね
If you ignore me, I might cry.
だってそんなの聞いてないぺこらちゃん
Because Pekora-chan didn't hear about that!
わかってるよねダーリン？
You understand, don't you, darling?
いっぱい愛をまつまつ！
Waiting for lots of love!
ノエル！ (もっと！) ぺこら！ (もっと！)
Noel! (More!) Pekora! (More!)
フレア！ (もっと！) マリン！ (もっと！)
Flare! (More!) Marine! (More!)
ホロライブファンタジーズを
We love...
愛してるー！♡
...Hololive Fantasies!
君のこと大好き大好き大好き
I love you, love you, love you,
大好き大好き！
love you, love you!
溢れるこの愛は きっとずっと止まらない
This overflowing love surely will never stop.
アイアイアイアイ I love you 君が
Ai ai ai ai, I love you, you are...
アイアイアイアイ I need you
Ai ai ai ai, I need you!
もっと もっと もっと もっと 君だけ愛させて
More, more, more, more, let me love only you.
ときめくハートごぴょんぴょんぴょん
Heart throbbing, five pyon-pyon-pyons!
矢に射たれてあんびょびょ こんなんなったら魔法は解けまーせん
Shot by an arrow, an-byo-byo! The magic won't break.
本気になってる ぬいぬいぬい
Getting serious, nui nui nui!
生きてるそばで アホイホイ
By your side as long as I live, ahoy hoi!
もっと もっと もっと もっと 好きなだけ愛してね
More, more, more, more, love me as much as you like.
アイアイアイアイ I love you
Ai ai ai ai, I love you!
アイアイアイアイ I need you
Ai ai ai ai, I need you!
アイアイアイアイ I love you
Ai ai ai ai, I love you!
アイアイアイアイ I need you
Ai ai ai ai, I need you!
私達の愛をもっと！
Give more of our love!
あんじゃピキピキ アホイ！ ピカチュキ アホイ！
Anja piki-piki ahoy! Pika-chuki ahoy!
お色気担当のマリンです！
I'm Marine, the one in charge of sex appeal!
ヤンフラ！ 踊るアホイに見るアホイ！
Yan-fura! Fools dancing and fools watching!
共に脱落にマリン召しませ
Let's fall together, please enjoy Marine.
おまり！ ナイス前兆だな
O-mari! Nice omen!
うさ耳透明？最強女神ぺこ！
Bunny ears transparent? The strongest goddess, Peko!
ぺこぺこら！ ママ！よしよしして！
Peko Peko-ra! Mama! Give me some pats!
ちょっと！欲張り目、横取りか？
Wait! You greedy one, trying to steal it?
れいでぃ？ うさぎか？ 大成功のため！
Lady? Rabbit? For the sake of a big success!
初見コールもいけちゃう？
Even the first-timer call is okay?
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol,
実家の安心感コールル
The relief of being home, call-ru.
おきまりのファンサービス 好き溢れちゃう
The usual fan service, love is overflowing.
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル 極めたおたげ踊るる
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol, dancing the ultimate wotagei.
新規もいる 古参いる
Newbies and veterans are here,
もはや推し変えなこてじゃん
you can't change your oshi now.
会いたい！ 推したい！
I want to meet you! I want to support you!
おきまりコールで！
With the usual call!
現場でテンプレおえきゅるきゅる
At the venue, the template 'oe' kyuru kyuru.
ちあー☆ちあー！ フレフレエルフレ！
Cheer cheer! Go go El-fure!
褒められてるやです
I'm being praised.
ハイだり！ ハイはに！ 世界で一番愛してる！
Hi-darling! Hi-honey! I love you more than anyone!
今ならチャンネル登録なんて無料！
Subscribing to the channel is free right now!
ジョイエンジョイ団長のノエル
Joy enjoy, Danchou Noel,
ゆるふわ脳筋女騎士だよ
the fluffy brain-muscle female knight.
王道見たい？ クラップでいたい？
Want to see the royal road? Want to be clapping?
ギュッ！ドン！
Gyu! Don!
いつものタイム自撮り
The usual time selfie,
歌詞より愛校正
proofreading love over lyrics.
あれ実質メンバー
That's practically a member.
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol,
ハートな振り付けもコピーるる
copying the heart choreography.
可愛いとか超えて 好きこじらせちゃう
Exceeding 'cute', my love is getting complicated.
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル 概念からも集める
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol, gathering even from concepts.
ガチ恋組もエル勢も もはや全員推し確定じゃん
Gachikoi and El-勢 groups, everyone's support is confirmed.
響きたい！ 乗りたい！ 現場で全通おえきゅるきゅる
Resonating! Riding along! Attending every show at the venue!
みんなの王様！
Everyone's king!
みんなの歌姫！
Everyone's diva!
みんなの団長！
Everyone's leader!
みんなの船長！
Everyone's captain!
Love and Peaceな時も
In times of Love and Peace,
推しがへこんだ時でも
and even when your oshi is feeling down,
トライアンドエラー重ねたい 君と見たい景色があるんだ
I want to keep trying, there's a scenery I want to see with you.
Ready Go!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol,
実家の安心感コールル
The relief of being home, call-ru.
おきまりのファンサービス 大好き一生好きだよ
The usual fan service, I love it, I'll love you forever!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol,
ラストまでおっかけルル
chasing you until the very end.
概念ことほ存在が 最強大優勝！
Conceptual celebration, our existence is the grand victory!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol,
永遠の愛誓える
I can vow eternal love.
単推ししてる箱推しは もはや生涯オタク確定じゃん
Solo or group supporters, you're life-long otaku now!
もうずっと もうずっと
Always and forever,
現場で限界おえきゅるきゅる
reaching the limit at the venue, 'oe' kyuru kyuru!
チア！チア！
Cheers! Cheers!
一生現場で...
Always at the scene...
...チア！
...cheers!
皆さん！イエーイ！
Everyone! Yay!
皆さん、イエーイ！
Everyone, yay!
ちょっと、安心しすぎた。
Wait, I relaxed a bit too much.
あ、暑い！
Ah, it's hot!
落ち着くために自己紹介しよう。
Let's introduce ourselves to calm down.
自己紹介、オッケー。
Introductions, okay.
そうだね、いけ。
That's right, go for it.
ぺこらから行きますよ！
Pekora's going first!
はい！
Yes!
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Kon-peko, kon-peko, kon-peko!
ホロライブ三期生の、兎田...
Hololive 3rd Gen's Usada...
...ぺこらぺこ！
...Pekora-peko!
って言わせてよー。言いたかったのにー！
Let me say it! I wanted to say it!
確かに、確かに。
True, true.
ちょっともう一回やってよ、もう一回。
Wait, do it again, one more time.
なんて言えばいいの、ぺこらは？
What should I say, Pekora?
じゃあ、「こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー」つったら、
Well, after I say "Kon-peko, kon-peko, kon-peko,"
あ、向こうも言いたいんだね。
Oh, they want to say it too.
そういうことね。
I see.
じゃあ、皆、言ってくれますかー？
So, will everyone say it for me?
やったー！
Yay!
じゃあ行きますよ！
Okay, here I go!
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Kon-peko, kon-peko, kon-peko!
いいよー！
Nice!
ホロライブ三期生の、兎田...
Hololive 3rd Gen's Usada...
...ぺこらぺこ！
...Pekora-peko!
はい、じゃあフレアは「こんぬい」じゃなくて、
Okay, then for Flare, instead of "Kon-nui,"
「ハイ、ダーリン」って言うから、「ハイ、ハニー」って返してくださーい！
I'll say "Hi, Darling," so please reply with "Hi, Honey!"
はい！
Okay!
はい。
Alright.
ハイ、ダーリン！
Hi, Darling!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ホロライブ三期生の、不知火フレアと！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shiranui Flare!
と！
And!
はい、じゃあ団長は、
Okay, then I'll say,
「牛丼はー？」って言うんで、
"How about beef bowls?"
「並盛りのー！」って言ってください。
So please say, "Regular size!"
お腹空いてるから。
Because I'm hungry.
じゃあ行くよ！
Alright, here I go!
牛丼はー？
How about beef bowls?
あ、イエーイ、そうだよねー！
Ah, yay, that's right!
ホロライブ三期生の、白銀ノエルと！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel!
と！
And!
君たち、今、もしかったら、
You guys... if by any chance,
フレアのこと「ハニー」って言った？
did you just call Flare "Honey"?
言ったよね？
You did, right?
お前ら！
You guys!
違う、お前ら！
No, you guys!
ヨロヨロ。
Staggering.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
団長のことは捨ててしまったのね、君たち。
So you've abandoned me, have you guys?
なんちゃって。
Just kidding.
え、じゃあどうしようかな。
Um, so what should I do?
あ、じゃあ普通に「アホイ」で行きますんで、
Oh, then I'll just go with the usual "Ahoy,"
「アホイ」って言ってくださーい！
so please say "Ahoy!"
はい！
Okay!
アホイー！
Ahoy!
誰がアホやー！
Who are you calling an idiot?!
なんちゃって。
Just kidding.
え、ホロライブ三期生、えっと、
Um, Hololive 3rd Gen, uh,
ド忘れしちゃった。
I completely forgot.
ホロライブ三期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の、
Hololive 3rd Gen, Captain of the Houshou Pirates,
宝鐘マリンです！
Houshou Marine-desu!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ドーン！
Boom!
イエーイ！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
せっかくだから、お、
Since we're here...
皆、なんかアイドル口上みたいなのさ、
Everyone, that idol-style self-intro,
練習したやつ、やる？
the one we practiced... shall we do it?
やる？
Do it?
やろうよ、これやるしかないでしょ！
Let's do it, we have to!
そうね、せっかく練習したし。
Yeah, since we practiced so hard.
じゃあ順番で。
Then, one by one.
あ、順番で行きましょう、順番で。
Ah, let's go in order, in order.
オッケー。
Okay.
皆覚えてるよね、ぺこらの口上。
Everyone remembers, right? Pekora's intro.
絶対覚えてねーぞ。
I bet they don't remember at all.
覚えてるよね、ちゃんと。
They remember, for sure.
覚えてる人、手挙げてー。
Those who remember, raise your hands!
覚えてる！
I remember!
めっちゃ声上がってるね、皆。
Everyone's cheering so loud.
全然覚えてねーって。
They say they don't remember at all.
じゃあ、今から覚えてくださいね！
Then, please learn it right now!
じゃあぺこらから行きますよ！
Okay, Pekora's going first!
ラビット！キャロット！キラッと登場！
Rabbit! Carrot! A sparkling entrance!
最強アイドルぺこらが来たぺこ！
The strongest idol, Pekora, is here-peko!
まだまだ続くよ...
It's far from over...
...ぺこら、スターライト！
...Pekora, Starlight!
めっちゃキラキラしてるー！
So sparkly!
ちょっと、フレア、めっちゃ難しいんだけどさ、
Wait, Flare's is really hard...
いけるかな、これ？
Can I pull this off?
いけるいける！
You can do it!
エルフレたちも、あ、掛け声とか、
Elfriends too, ah, the calls and such,
大丈夫だよ！
it'll be fine!
これ、皆にもコールアンドレスポンスして欲しくて、
I want everyone to do the call-and-response,
あの...
um...
「準備は？」って言ったら「万端！」
When I say "Ready?", say "All set!"
「コールは？」って聞くので「簡単！」
When I ask "Call?", say "Easy!"
「手拍子！」パンパン！
"Clapping!" (Clap, clap!)
「ステップ！」簡単！
"Step!" Easy!
「私は？」ふーたん！
"Who am I?" Fuu-tan!
めっちゃ難しいだろ！
That's way too hard!
めっちゃハードル高い！
The bar is so high!
これ練習ね、練習。
This is practice, practice.
はい、覚えてくださいね。
Yes, please remember it.
では、行きますよ！
Now, here I go!
うん。
Yup.
こんぬーい！準備は？
Kon-nuui! Ready?
コールは？
Call?
手拍子！
Clapping!
ステップ！
Step!
私は？
Who am I?
ホロライブ三期生、不知火フレアです！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Shiranui Flare-desu!
おおー、すごい！
Oh, amazing!
すごーい、お見事！
Amazing, perfect!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
難しいのにすごいですよー！
That was impressive despite being hard!
じゃあ、次はノエル！
Okay, next is Noel!
ノエル行きます！
Noel's going!
団長、コールアンドレスポンス無いから、
I don't have a call-and-response,
ちょっとラップします！
so I'll do a little rap!
ラップ！
Rap!
一等角からここまで！
From the very edge to here!
じゃあ、こっから...
So, from here...
...行こうかな！
...I'll go!
行きます！
Here I go!
メインなし質問思考の、
Thinking about questions without a lead,
食べ物答えは牛丼、
the answer to food is beef bowl,
おろしで飲み物皆の球根、
grated radish as a drink, everyone's bulb,
ダメダメ重婚！
No, no bigamy!
ホロライブ三期生、白銀ノエルでーす！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Shirogane Noel-desu!
はい、じゃあマリン！
Okay, next is Marine!
マリンは恒例なんですが先に予習しましょうか。
Marine is a regular, but let's practice first.
マリンが「マリンは？」って言ったら君たちは「船長！」
When Marine says "Marine is?", you say "Captain!"
で、「君たちは？」「一味！」
Then, "You are?" "Crew!"
「我ら無敵の？」「海賊団！」
And "We are the invincible?" "Pirates!"
で最後に「宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです」って言うから
And finally, I'll say "I'm the Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine"
そしたら問答無用で「かわいい！」って言う。
so then without question, say "Cute!"
わかりましたね？
Got it?
まあ、余裕だよね。
Well, it's a breeze, right?
はい素晴らしい返事できて丸。
Yes, great response, perfect score.
じゃあ行きますよ！
Alright, here we go!
マリンはー？
Marine is—?
船長ー！
Captain—!
君たちはー？
You are—?
一味ー！
Crew—!
我ら無敵のー？
We are the invincible—?
海賊団ー！
Pirates—!
宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです！
Captain of the Houshou Pirates, I'm Houshou Marine!
かわいいー！
Cute—!
いや、気持ちいいねこれ。
Man, this feels good.
そんな可愛い。
So cute.
よかったなぁ、可愛いって言われて。
I'm glad you were called cute.
そんなことないけど…
It's not really like that, but...
でもコール＆レスポンスね
But the call and response,
ちょっと一発目からもうすごい難しいのやらせちゃってどうもすみませんね。
sorry for making you do such a difficult one right from the start.
ねー。
Right.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ええ声が聞こえますよ、いただきました。
I can hear your voices, thank you.
さっきのさ、うちらの円陣聞こえました？
Earlier, did you hear our pep rally?
あー聞こえた！
Ah, you heard it!
やったー！
Yay!
ちょっと、なんか聞こえるかなって不安だったんだよね。
I was a bit worried if it would be heard.
こっちにはね君らの声よく聞こえるんだけど
We can hear your voices well from here,
さすがにマイク通さないとちっちゃかったかなと思って。
but I thought it might be too quiet without microphones.
いや、お腹から出した。
No, it came from the gut.
あ、聞こえた？
Oh, you heard it?
ありがとう！聞こえるよ！
Thank you! We can hear you!
こっちにも声聞こえてますよ！
We can hear your voices too!
衣装のことも言わなきゃ。
We have to talk about the outfits too.
そうだよ、そうだよ。
That's right, that's right.
突然の新衣装、可愛いでしょ。
New outfits all of a sudden, they're cute, right?
ちょっとずつ違うところがありますんで。
There are slight differences between them.
これ、よく見てない？
Look closely, okay?
ぺこらは耳輪っかがついているぺこです！
Pekora has a halo ring on her ear!
なんと発案者はノエちゃん！
And Noel-chan was the one who came up with it!
そう、ノエル！
Yes, Noel!
すごいでしょ？
Amazing, right?
かわいい！
Cute!
え、出しました。
Uh, I showed it.
マリンはねヘッドドレスがね、ほらこんな感じで
Marine has this headdress, look, it's like this,
バツバツバツバツバツってなってるの。
it has all these X's on it.
かわいい！
Cute!
団長なんかポンポンついてます。
Captain, you've got some pom-poms.
なんか、ふわふわ、ふわふわしてる。
They're, like, fluffy, fluffy.
フレアはこの頭のリボンかな。
For Flare, it's this ribbon on the head.
かわいいね。
Cute, isn't it?
あと皆と色が違いますね、靴下。
Also, the color of the socks is different from everyone else's.
そう、フレアはギャルじゃないんで。
Yeah, Flare isn't a gyaru, you see.
私らギャル！
We're gyaru!
ぺこらもギャル！
Pekora's also a gyaru!
ギャルです！
I'm a gyaru!
ちなみに、皆さん…
By the way, everyone...
うちらね、結構めちゃめちゃ喋りすぎてるみたいで。
it seems we've been talking way too much.
あ、やばい！やばい！
Ah, crap! Crap!
このまま音楽しないのかい？みたいなことを。
Like, "Aren't you going to play music?"
そうだよね、スタッフさんに言われてますけれど。
That's true, the staff is telling us that.
でも、ちなみに、あの配信で見てる方、
But, by the way, those watching the stream,
YouTubeで見てる方。
those watching on YouTube.
概要欄にね、配信チケットのリンクありますので。
There's a link for streaming tickets in the description.
ぜひ、あの次の曲でちょっとチラ見せが終わる。
Please do, the sneak peek ends after the next song.
あ、そうだよ！
Ah, that's right!
終わっちゃうので今のうちに。
It's ending, so get them now.
そう、まだ見てほしいパートがいっぱいあるんです、ぜひ！
Yes, there are still many parts we want you to see, so please!
お願いします！
Please!
ハッシュタグ「#きゅるるん大作戦DAY1」でいっぱい呟いてね！
Tweet a lot using the hashtag #KyurulunDaisakusenDAY1!
お願いします！
Please!
ていうか、その、これもやらないと。
Actually, we have to do this too.
あのね、生バンドがね、すごいかっこいいじゃない？
You know, the live band is really cool, right?
うん、そうだね。
Yeah, true.
だからちょっと聞かせたくて。
So I wanted you to hear them a bit.
じゃあ、ぺこらちゃんから言ってもらっていいですか？
So, Pekora-chan, could you go first?
了解！
Roger!
エアバンド、キーボード担当、兎田ぺこら！
Air band, Keyboard, Usada Pekora!
おお、すげー！
Oh, amazing!
行くよ、ギター、宝鐘マリン！
Here I go! Guitar, Houshou Marine!
おー、かっこいい！
Oh, cool!
はい、ドラム、白銀ノエル！
Alright, Drums, Shirogane Noel!
やばい、かっこよ！
Crazy, so cool!
じゃあ、フレア、ベースやります！
Then, Flare will do the Bass!
おお、かっこいい！
Oh, cool!
演奏してます！
We're playing!
あ、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょうか。
Ah, let's move on to the next song soon.
場所場所！
Positions, positions!
はい、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょう！
Alright, let's start the next song!
せーの！
One, two!
リアリティ・ファンタジー！
Reality Fantasy!
H-O-L-O-L-I-V-E
L-I-V-E
F-A-N-T-A-S-Y
冒険　出発さ
Adventure, time to set off
挑戦　開始さ
Challenge, time to start
さあ冒険　出発さ
Now, adventure, time to set off
挑戦　開始さ
Challenge, time to start
さあ冒険　出発さ
Now, adventure, time to set off
挑戦　開始さ　さあ
Challenge, time to start, now
お宝探しに　大海原へいざ出航だ
To find treasure, setting sail for the vast ocean
冒険！出発！
Adventure! Departure!
さぁ、挑戦！開始！さぁ！
Now, challenge! Start! Now!
挑戦！開始！
Challenge! Start!
身も心もぴょんぴょん
Body and soul jumping
ワクワク　頂上頂上
Excitement, to the top, top
冒険！出発！
Adventure! Departure!
さぁ、挑戦！開始！さぁ！
Now, challenge! Start! Now!
挑戦！開始！
Challenge! Start!
水平線向こう側
Beyond the horizon,
新天地待っててね
wait for us, new land
運命なんて飛び越して
Jump over destiny
その先へ
and go beyond
さぁ　リアリティ　ファンタジー
Now, reality and fantasy
二つの狭間で
In the gap between the two
夢歌え　越えたくて一緒に
Sing your dreams, wanting to overcome together
さぁ　まだ見ぬ世界へと
Now, to a world yet unseen,
君を連れて行くよ
I'll take you with me
みんなが繋がる物語
A story where everyone is connected,
さぁ始まるよ
now it begins
冒険！出発！
Adventure! Departure!
さぁ、挑戦！開始！さぁ！
Now, challenge! Start! Now!
冒険！出発！
Adventure! Departure!
さぁ、挑戦！開始！さぁ！
Now, challenge! Start! Now!
みんなの志　抱き
With everyone's ambition,
挑もう騎士団集合
let's challenge, Knight Order assemble
冒険！出発！
Adventure! Departure!
さぁ、挑戦！開始！さぁ！
Now, challenge! Start! Now!
胸に宿る太陽
The sun in my chest,
風を切ってさらに輝け
cut through the wind and shine even more
冒険！出発！
Adventure! Departure!
さぁ、挑戦！開始！さぁ！
Now, challenge! Start! Now!
迷走と夢　晴天に
Straying and dreams, to the clear sky
掲げたら突撃だ
if we hold them up, it's a charge
寄せては断つ　この旅見守って
Gathering and cutting off, watch over this journey
さぁ　リアリティ　ファンタジー
Now, reality and fantasy
二つの狭間で
In the gap between the two
帆を上げて　向かえユートピアへ
Raise the sails, head for Utopia
さぁ　それぞれの世界から
Now, from each of our worlds
垣根を越えたら
Once we cross the fences
みんなが繋がる物語
A story where everyone is connected,
さぁ始まるよ
now it begins
明るく陽気に　新たな海原　ホロライブ
Cheerful and lively, new ocean, Hololive
愛嬌開放　ウサ耳澄まして　ホロライブ
Charm unleashed, rabbit ears perked up, Hololive
騎士道と誇り　胸に刻んだら　ホロライブ
Bushido and pride, once carved in the chest, Hololive
神話に歌われる　神秘のささやき　ホロライブ
Sung in myths, whispers of mystery, Hololive
冒険！出発！
Adventure! Departure!
さぁ、挑戦！開始！さぁ！
Now, challenge! Start! Now!
さぁ　リアリティ　ファンタジー
Now, reality and fantasy
二つの狭間で
In the gap between the two
夢歌え　越えたくて一緒に
Sing your dreams, wanting to overcome together
さぁ　まだ見ぬ世界へと
Now, to a world yet unseen,
君を連れて行くよ
I'll take you with me
準備はほらできたよ
See, the preparation is done,
ルートも先回ったよ
I've also gone ahead on the route
みんなが繋がる物語
A story where everyone is connected,
さぁ始まるよ
now it begins
時は2026年。
The year is 2026.
2回目の3期生ライブ。
The second 3rd Generation live.
このチャンスを逃してなるものか。
I cannot let this chance slip away.
今こそ、全人類兎化計画を...
Now is the time to... Humanity's Rabbitification Project...
...遂行する！
...execute!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peak part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
世界は変わってゆく
The world keeps on changing
僕らの物語
In this story of ours
いつまでも終わらない
It will never end
この夢の続きを
The continuation of this dream
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!